<overviews>
	<all-packages>
		<description><![CDATA[
			<div id="shortIntroduction">
				<p>
					The nanosome-util project contains core ActionScript 3 util to
					improve the quality or performance of applications or frameworks.
					We limit it to the utils necessary to develop our nanosome projects.
					This covers fast dispatching, disposing, anonymous object access
					and alike.
				</p>
			</div> 
		]]></description>
	</all-packages>
	<packages>
		<package name="nanosome.util" >
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[
				Contains general utils used by various nanosome projects.
			]]></shortDescription>
			<description><![CDATA[
				<p>
					General util for working with flash: language structures, core
					interfaces, etc. 
				</p>
			]]></description>
		</package>
		<package name="nanosome.access" >
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[
				Contains functionality for reading/writing annonymous objects.
			]]></shortDescription>
			<description><![CDATA[
				<p>
					Many parts of nanosome deal with annonymous objects. When dealing
					with annonymous objects there are many small traps that can be
					easily forgot. Beside that writing it seperatly in all cases makes
					it easy to have inconsitant behaviours and in some cases its even
					slower to implement it directly.
				</p>
			]]></description>
		</package>
		<package name="nanosome.util.list" >
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[
				Contains fast link lists used for notifications of listeners or
				similar use cases.
			]]></shortDescription>
			<description><![CDATA[
				<p>
					When working with listeners its not a good idea to try to implement
					the lists to store and access lists for each case again since it
					has plenty of cases that are neighter easy to implement nor easy
					to debug. The implementations in this package should allow fast,
					easy to use well tested lists.
				</p>
			]]></description>
		</package>
		<package name="nanosome.util.normalize" >
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[
				Package for algorithms to work with normalized numbers.
			]]></shortDescription>
			<description><![CDATA[
				<p>
					It is reasonable to store and work internally with normalized numbers
					when working with ranged values. This package offers a set of
					algorithms to deal with them in a standard way, providing essential
					functionalities for other nanosome projects.
				</p>
			]]></description>
		</package>
		
		<package name="nanosome.pool" >
			<shortDescription><![CDATA[
				Contains utils to work with instance pools.
			]]></shortDescription>
			<description><![CDATA[
				Instance pools are easily implemented as lists. This package offers
				functionality to reduce the amount of code when working with
				instance pools.
			]]></description>
		</package>
	</packages>
</overviews>